A Guide to the Ford Foundation records, Staff Subject Files, Jon Funabiki FA1447
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Media, Arts, and Culture (MAC) Grant Materials, 1992-2007; 1
  - Media and Journalism, 1992-2007; 1
    - Atlanta Unity '94 Convention (3 folders), 1995-2000 (Box 27, Folder 213-215)
      Grant No: 9701347, 9701349,9701350, 9701352, 9701373, 9501237
    - Bay Area Institute, 1996-1999 (Box 27, Folder 216)
      Grant No: 9600477
    - Bay Area Institute, 1993-1998 (Box 27, Folder 217)
      Grant No: 9450174
    - Bay Area Institute - Pacific News Service-New California Media Expo (2 folders), 1997-2001 (Box 27, Folder 218-219)
    - Camera News, Inc. - The Black Press: Soldiers without Swords (4 folders), 1996-1998 (Box 27, Folder 220, Box 28, Folder 221-223)
      Grant No.: 980-0520, 960-0940, 960-0949
    - Compass Point (Support Center for Nonprofit Management) - Technical Assistance (4 folders), 1998-1999 (Box 28, Folder 224-227)
      Grant No.: 980-1122
    - Communications Consortium Media Center (CCMC) - Communications Strategies and Brochure (2 folders), 1998-2001 (Box 28, Folder 228-229)
      Grant No.: 09801123
    - Children Now - Children, Race, Media Study, 1997-1999 (Box 28, Folder 230)
      Grant No.: 980-0579
    - Children Now - "The Local News Media's Picture of Children" (3 folders), 1998-2001 (Box 29, Folder 231-233)
      Grant No.: 1000-0513
    - Center for Educational Telecommunications - Ancestors in the Americas (2 folders), 1997-1999 (Box 29, Folder 234-235)
      Grant No. 9701099 - Part I: Coolies, Sailors, Settlers; Part II: Chinese in the Frontier West
    - Emory University - "Press and Public: Improving Understanding" (2 folders), 1998-2001 (Box 29, Folder 236-237)
      Grant No.: 9801265
    - Fred Friendly Seminars, Inc. - Disconnected: Politics, the Press, and the Public (3 folders), 1999-2000 (Box 29, Folder 238-240)
      Grant No.: 9901722
    - Garrett-Evangelical Theological Seminary - Center for Religion and the News Media (3 folders), 1998-2000 (Box 29, Folder 241-243)
      Grant No: 09800956
    - Harvard University - Howard Gardner (4 folders), 1997-1998 (Box 30, Folder 244-247)
      Grant No.: 9750807
    - International Women's Media Foundation (2 folders), 1998-2001 (Box 30, Folder 248-249)
      Grant No.: 9800579; 09900339
    - Advertising Council, Inc. #920-0863, 1992-1998 (Box 58, Folder 496-498)
    - Benton Foundation, 1996 (Box 58, Folder 499, Box 59, Folder 500)
    - Black Journalist Association of Southern California, 1992-1998 (Box 59, Folder 501-502)
      Grant numbers: 940-1122 and 935-0267
    - Columbia University Southern Asian Institute, 1996 (Box 59, Folder 503)
      Grant Number: 965-1034
    - Family Communications, Inc., 1993-1995 (Box 59, Folder 504-506)
      Grant Numbers: 920-0480 and 930-0480
    - Greater Philadelphia Urban Affairs Coalition, 1994-1995 (Box 59, Folder 507-508)
      Grant Number: 940-0459
    - Institute for Alternative Journalism, 1996 (Box 60, Folder 509)
      Grant Number: 965-0369
    - The State University of Iowa, 1995-1996 (Box 60, Folder 510)
      Grant Number: 955-1065
    - Mississippi Authority for Educational Television, 1994-1995 (Box 60, Folder 511)
      Grant Number: 940-1084
    - National Council of La Raza, 1994-1998 (Box 60, Folder 512)
      Grant Number: 955-0575
    - The National Latino Communications Consortium, 1993-1997 (Box 60, Folder 513-514)
      Grant Number: 920-0603
    - Ortiz/Simon Productions, 1994-1996 (Box 60, Folder 515)
      Grant Number: 940-0325
    - Radio Bilingue, Inc., 1992-1997 (Box 61, Folder 516)
      Grant Number: 860-0209
    - Upstream Productions, 1997-1998 (Box 61, Folder 517)
      Grant Number: 970-1098
    - Vera Institute of Justice, Inc., 1992-1998 (Box 61, Folder 518-519)
      Grant Number: 965-0585
    - William Greaves Productions, 1993 (Box 61, Folder 520)
      Grant Number: 920-0868
    - WGBH Educational Foundation, 1993-1998 (Box 61, Folder 521-522)
      Grant Numbers: 930-0612,945-0365
  - Arts and Culture, 2003-2006; 2
    - Spartacus, 2003-2004 (Box 30, Folder 250)
    - Sringaram - Dance of Love, a Film by Sharada Ramanathan, 2006 (Box 30, Folder 251)
    - Sharada Ramanathan Correspondence, 2005 (Box 30, Folder 252)
- Media, Arts, and Culture (MAC) Administrative Office Files, Meetings, and Reports, 1990-2007; 2
  - Becky Lentz Memos (3 folders), 2001-2005 (Box 31, Folder 253-255)
  - Budgeting, Reserves, Etc., 2001-2003 (Box 31, Folder 256)
    U.S. Bank Visa, Corporate Credit Card Program User's Guide; New Expense Reporting System; Expense Type Lists; General Terms and Entitlements of Consultants to the Ford Foundation; Ford Foundation Pools Glossary
  - Ford Management Meetings, 2003-2004 (Box 31, Folder 257)
  - Orlando Bagwell - Correspondence and Memos, 2003-2004 (Box 31, Folder 258)
  - Media, Arts, and Culture - Learning Circle Meeting in Ghana, 2004 (Box 31, Folder 259)
  - Public Engagement, 2002-2004 (Box 31, Folder 260)
  - Program Officer Memos, 1999 (Box 32, Folder 261)
  - Media, Arts, and Culture Learning (2 folders), 2005-2006 (Box 32, Folder 262-263)
  - Education, Media, Arts, and Culture (EMAC) Worldwide Meeting, 2002 (Box 32, Folder 264)
    Notes and memos
  - Knowledge, Creativity, and Freedom (KCF) - Retreat, 2005 (Box 32, Folder 265)
  - Knowledge, Creativity, and Freedom (KCF) - South Africa, 2004 (Box 32, Folder 266)
  - Knowledge, Creativity, and Freedom (KCF) - Trustees, 2006 May (Box 32, Folder 267)
  - Ford Foundation Joint Worldwide Meeting, 2002 (Box 32, Folder 268)
  - Media Program Reorganization, undated (Box 33, Folder 269)
  - Media, Arts and Culture Administrative, 2000-2004 (Box 33, Folder 270)
    Notes, correspondence, calendars, and proposals - MAC Conversations
  - Media, Arts and Culture Communications, 2005 (Box 33, Folder 271)
  - Media, Arts and Culture Vision/Media Vision (3 folders), 1998-2004 (Box 33, Folder 272-274)
  - Media, Arts and Culture Global Meetings (3 folders), 2002 (Box 33, Folder 275-277)
  - Media, Arts and Culture Ghana (3 folders), 2001-2004 (Box 34, Folder 278-280)
    Includes Oakland MAC Learning Group Meeting Report 2002; The Ford Foundation's Media and Arts and Culture Grantmaking: An Historical Profile, 1951-2001; Global Exchange of Ideas: The African Marketplace; The Arts of Africa in the Twenty First Century; Biographies and presentations; meeting info; Regional Programming in Africa and The Middle East; International Centre for African Music and Dance; KCF: MAC Learning Circle Meeting; Shopping in Accra
  - Media - Assets (3 folders), 2002-2003 (Box 34, Folder 281-283)
  - Program Associate Policies, Procedures, and Selections (2 folders), 2002-2004 (Box 34, Folder 284-285)
  - Program Associates Program Review (2 folders), 1999-2003 (Box 35, Folder 286-287)
  - Media, Arts, and Culture - Invitations and Postcards, 1990-2000 (Box 35, Folder 288)
  - Danny Pearl Foundation, 2003 (Box 35, Folder 289)
  - Media Diversity Institute, 2001-2003 (Box 35, Folder 290)
    Publications and notes
  - Pen American Center - Freedom to Write Program, 2002 (Box 35, Folder 291)
  - Free Expression (4 folders), 2003-2004 (Box 35, Folder 292, Box 36, Folder 293-295)
    Third Annual Worldwide Press Freedom Index; International Communications Forum; World Media Assembly, Sarajevo 2000; Terraviva UN Journal; World Press Freedom Committee; Office of the Special Rapporteur for Freedom of Expression: Inter-American Commission on Human Rights pamphlets (English and Spanish); Office of the Special Rapporteur for Freedom of Expression: Inter-American Commission on Human Rights - In the News: Samples of Coverage of the Special Rapporteur's activities all around the hemisphere; Office of the Special Rapporteur for Freedom of Expression: Inter-American Commission on Human Rights - Panama and Haiti States Reports 2003 and Preliminary observations on Mexico and Honduras; Annual Report of the Inter-American Commission on Human Rights 2002 Volume III; Office of the Special Rapporteur for Freedom of Expression: Inter-American Commission on Human Rights Press Releases 2003 Samples; RCFP White Paper - Homefront Confidential Fourth Edition; New Code Words for Censorship: Modern Labels for Curbs on the Press; Press Freedom on the Internet, Conference Summary 2003; Reporters without Borders - 2003 Global Press Freedom World Tour; How to Use the Federal FOI Act 9th Edition
  - Reporter Without Borders, 2003-2004 (Box 36, Folder 296)
  - Aspen Mission - Communication and Society Program Conference Readings (4 folders), 2000-2001 (Box 36, Folder 297-298, Box 37, Folder 299-300)
    Includes: Mission Driven Media: Not Just Survival, but Success; Leading Change in the News Media: Closing the Press-Public Disconnect; Strategies for Supporting Sustainable Media Pluralism; Mission-Driven Media: Not Just Survival, But Success; New Voices, New Media Vehicles: Revitalizing the National Dialogue Conference Readings; correspondence
  - American Indian Research and Grants Assessment Project: A Report to the Committee on Indigenous Peoples, Final Working Draft, 2001 July (Box 37, Folder 301)
    Submitted by The Harvard Project on American Indian, Economic Development, John F. Kennedy School of Government, Harvard University; First Nations Development Institute; The Udall Center for Studies in Public Policy, University of Arizona; Project Sounding Board
  - Quality Time?: The Report of the Twentieth Century Fund Task Force on Public Television with Background Paper by Richard Somerset-Ward, 1993 (Box 37, Folder 302)
  - Transition: An International Review, V8N1, Issue 77 - The New Sex Tourism, undated (Box 37, Folder 303)
  - Profiles of Ethnic Media: California's New Civic Communicators, A Report by New California Media for MAC, 2002 (Box 37, Folder 304)
  - Grant Makers Orientation 2000 Notebook (Box 37, Folder 305)
  - An Explanation of The Citizen's Guide to the Airwaves, J. H. Snider, 2003 (Box 38, Folder 306)
  - Guide to Research on Race and News, The Missouri School of Journalism, 2000 (Box 38, Folder 307)
  - The Southern California Conference on The Media and the Law, 1977 (Box 38, Folder 308)
  - The State of Public Radio: A Report to the Ford Foundation, 2001 October (Box 38, Folder 309)
    Reversioned for public distribution 8/02, Dennis Hamilton, David Othmer, Skip Pizzi, Nan Rubin
  - Covering Crime and Justice Guide Correspondence, 2005 (Box 38, Folder 310)
  - International Freedom of Expression Exchange (IFEX) - Clearing House, 2005 (Box 38, Folder 311)
  - National Public Radio Reports, 2002 (Box 38, Folder 312)
  - Dance Theatre of Harlem: Situation Analysis Reports and Correspondence, 2004-2005 (Box 38, Folder 313)
  - Earth Journalism Network (EJN) - Emails and Correspondence with James Fahn, 2004-2005 (Box 38, Folder 314)
  - Center for Public Integrity, 2005 (Box 38, Folder 315)
  - Board of Trustees (3 folders), 2003 January (Box 38, Folder 316-317, Box 39, Folder 318)
    January 2003 Board Meeting - The Ford Foudation's Special Initiative for Africa Discussion Paper; The Ford Foundation's Program Related Investment Fund Discussion Paper; Schedule; Biographies; The Philanthropic Response to 9/11: A Report Prepared for the Ford Foundation by Tom Seessel; Report to the Ranking Minority Member, Committee on Finance, US Senate - September 11: More Effective Collaboration Could Enhance Charitable Organizations' Contributions in Disasters; The Transition of the East European Program Discussion Paper; Racism and Metropolitan Dynamics: The Civil Rights Challenge of the 21st Century August 2002; Two Towns of Jasper; Docket Part I: List of Grant Actions, Annual Meeting of the Board of Trustees January 30, 2003; Docket Part II - Fiscal Reports and Recommended Action January 30, 2003; Ford Foundation Report 2003
  - The Double Bottom Line (DBL) Media Industry: An Analysis - A Report by the Investors' Circle Foundation, 2004 October (Box 39, Folder 319)
  - The State of Public Radio: A Report to the Ford Foundation (2 copies), 2001 October (Box 39, Folder 320)
  - The Ford Foundation Glossary of Pools (From FY2003 Grant Budgets), The Office of Management Services (Box 39, Folder 321)
  - Whassup?: Charting MAC's Next Decade, 2003 (Box 39, Folder 322)
  - Media, Arts and Culture Learning Circle Meeting, Accra, Ghana, 2004 February 9-13 (Box 39, Folder 323)
  - Global Perspectives in a Digital Age, 2004 (Box 39, Folder 324)
  - Discussion Papers Meetings, 2004 (Box 39, Folder 325)
    The Ford Foundation's Program in West Africa Discussion Paper; Transforming an American Region: Recommendations for a Gulf Coast Development Initiative: A Management Report to the Ford Foundation
  - Anti-Semitism Reports, 2004 April-May (Box 39, Folder 326)
    Drafts - A Report to the Ford Foundation by Myra Dinnerstein; Understanding and Combating Antisemitism in Europe Observations Prepared for Convening on May 12, 2004 in Brussels, Irena Grudzinska Gross
  - New Orleans - Post-Katrina Partial Report, undated (Box 39, Folder 327)
  - Diversity Initiative, 2004 May (Box 39, Folder 328)
    Strengthening Our Attention to Diversity: Recommendations from Foundation Staff - A Report, Prepared by the Global Forum on Women and Social Change, Constance Buchanan
  - Emerging Communities in The Philadelphia Suburbs, Junko Chano, undated (Box 39, Folder 329)
  - Douglas Gould and Co. Report: Religion and Media, 2001 (Box 39, Folder 330)
  - Convening of the Media, Arts and Culture Learning Group, Oakland, California, 2002 October 24-26 (Box 39, Folder 331)
  - Ford Foundation Cross Programme Meeting - Freedom of Expression and Democratisation of the Media, Steve Buckley, 2004 (Box 40, Folder 332)
  - Ford Foundation - Aspen Institute - International Roundtable on Journalism and Freedom of Expression, Queenstown, Maryland, 2003 November 12-14 (Box 40, Folder 333)
  - Media-On-Media, Dinah Eng, 2002 May 13 (Box 40, Folder 334)
  - Background Notes on Globalization, Identity and Development, Amartya Sen, Ford Foundation Joint Worldwide Meeting, 2002 (Box 40, Folder 335)
  - MAC Media Programming: 2004 and Beyond - Discussion Paper (Box 40, Folder 336)
  - Local Television News Ethics Study of News Directors and the American Public, Journalism Ethics and Integrity Project, The Radio and Television News Directors Foundation, undated (Box 40, Folder 337)
  - 2003 Local Television News Study of News Directors and the American Public, Journalism Ethics Project, Radio and Television News Directors Foundation (Box 40, Folder 338)
  - The Ford Foundation's Special Initiative for Africa - Discussion Paper, 2005 January (Box 40, Folder 339)
  - The Ford Foundation Program in the Andean Region and Southern Cone - Discussion Paper, 2004 September (Box 40, Folder 340)
  - Ford Foundation-Aspen Institute - International Roundtable Journalism and Freedom of Expression, Santiago, Chile, Prepared by Jon Funabiki, 2001 March 13-16 (Box 40, Folder 341)
  - Akiyoshi ITO, Miracles Under the Waves, Smithsonian Institution, undated (Box 40, Folder 342)
  - The Ford Foundation, First Bank Visa Corporate Credit Card Program Implementation Guide, 1997 February (Box 40, Folder 343)
  - The Ford Foundation FY 2004-2005 Biennial Worldwide Grant Budget Projections (Box 40, Folder 344)
  - Strengthening Foundation Accountability: Summary of the Vector III Recommendations, 2006 March (Box 40, Folder 345)
  - The Ford Foundation Glossary of Pools (From FY2005 Grant Budgets) (Box 40, Folder 346)
  - The Ford Foundation, Education, Knowledge and Religion Unit Breakout Meeting, The Getty Museum, 1999 January 7 (Box 53, Folder 457)
  - An Inquiry into News Media Criticism (Craig Lamay) (2 folders), 1999 August (Box 40, Folder 347-348)
    Report and appendices
  - Media Program (2 folders), 1995 (Box 41, Folder 349-350)
  - 2003 Local Television News Study of News Directors and the American Public, Journalism Ethics Project (Box 41, Folder 351)
  - Trustees Presentation, 2003 May (Box 41, Folder 352)
    Presentation notes and Preliminary Spending Level and Budget Fiscal Years 2004 and 2005 Biennium
  - Trustees (2 folders), 2003 September (Box 41, Folder 353-354)
    KCF Trustee Committee Meeting; Newsletters; Discussion Papers; International Fellowships Program Report 2003-2004; Proposed Fiscal Years 2004 and 2005 Spending Level and Proposed Program Support, Investment Management, General Management and Capital Projects Appropriations for Fiscal Year 2004
  - Trustees, 2004 January (Box 41, Folder 355)
  - Ford Foundation-Aspen Institute - International Roundtable on Journalism and Freedom of Expression - Stone Soup Meeting Materials (6 folders), 2002-2003 (Box 41, Folder 356-357, Box 42, Folder 358-361)
    Principles and Practice of a Free and Responsible Press: Lessons from Societies in Conflict and Transition, Craig L. LaMay; correspondence; conference readings; The State of the Arab Media 2003 - The Fight for Democracy; press articles; Pre-Conference Questionnaire; Summary of Conference by Jon Funabiki; group photo; participant biographies
  - Council on Foundations Conference Committee, 2000-2002 (Box 42, Folder 362)
  - Consultants' Biographies (Restricted), 2004 February (Box 52, Folder 456)
    Sensitive materials
  - Ethnic and Online News Media Explorations (2 folders), 1997-2006 (Box 42, Folder 363-364)
    Press materials; research papers; meeting notes
  - Cruel Justice Event, undated (Box 42, Folder 365)
  - Grantmakers in Film and Electronic Media (GFEM), 2005-2006 (Box 43, Folder 366)
  - International Convention on Cultural Diversity - France, 2003-2004 (Box 43, Folder 367)
  - Gulf/Katrina Initiative - Media (3 folders), 2005-2006 (Box 43, Folder 368-370)
    Press materials concerning race, reports, correspondence, Gulf Transformative Initiative, News Orleans Virtual Diaspora Network Follow-Up, Ford Foundation and Katrina, memos
  - Communications Network (6 folders), 2000-2005 (Box 43, Folder 371-373, Box 44, Folder 374-376)
  - Journalism Funders (4 folders), 2002-2003 (Box 44, Folder 377-380)
    Reports and notes; Meeting materials
  - Committee on Indigenous Peoples, 2001 (Box 44, Folder 381)
  - Center for Social Media, 2005 (Box 44, Folder 382)
  - Citizens Journalism, 2005 September (Box 45, Folder 383)
  - JusticeMakers Implementation - Media and Social Justice (3 folders), 2003-2004 (Box 45, Folder 384-386)
  - New York Regional Association of Grantmakers (NYRAG) (10 folders), 2002-2006 (Box 45, Folder 387-391, Box 46, Folder 392-396)
    Meeting materials, publications, strategic planning, financial statements, report, memos
  - Media-On-Media: A Report on a Meeting Examining How the Power of the Media Can Be Used to Help the Public Understand the Media, Dinah Eng, 2002 May 13 (Box 46, Folder 397)
  - Media Big Bet - Public Media Working Groups and Meetings, 2005 (Box 46, Folder 398)
  - Media Funders Initiatives (4 folders), 2002-2004 (Box 47, Folder 399-402)
  - Media - International, Freedom of Expression Reports (4 folders), 1999-2006 (Box 47, Folder 403-405, Box 48, Folder 406)
  - Conference Readings - International Roundtable on Journalism and Freedom of Expression - Funding Global Media: Models and Options, Queenstown, MD, 2003 November 12-14 (Box 48, Folder 407)
  - Reporters Without Borders - The 2003 Global Press Freedom World Tour, 2004 May (Box 48, Folder 408)
  - Reporters Without Borders - Dominique Issermann for Press Freedom, 2004 March (Box 48, Folder 409)
  - Mission-Driven Media Strategic Plan (Request for Proposals) - Creative Artists Agency, undated (Box 48, Folder 410)
  - Mission-Driven Media Strategic Plan (Request for Proposals) - Melissa Bradley - New Capitalist, Inc., 2002-2003 (Box 48, Folder 411)
  - Mission-Driven Media Strategic Plan (Request for Proposals) - Investor's Circle, 2002-2003 (Box 48, Folder 412)
  - Mission-Driven Media Strategic Plan (Request for Proposals) - Rudolf Steiner Foundation, 2003 (Box 48, Folder 413)
  - Mission-Driven Media Strategic Plan (Request for Proposals) - Calvert Foundation, 2002-2003 (Box 48, Folder 414)
  - Mission-Driven Media Strategic Plan (Request for Proposals) - Brody Weiser Burns, 2003 (Box 48, Folder 415)
  - Mission-Driven Media Strategic Plan (Request for Proposals) - Teymour Farman-Farmaian, 2003 (Box 48, Folder 416)
  - Mission-Driven Media Strategic Plan (Request for Proposals) - The Aspen Institute, 2002 (Box 48, Folder 417)
  - Best Practices, 1996 (Box 48, Folder 418)
  - Independent Press Development Fund Proposal to the Ford Foundation, 2005 February 22 (Box 48, Folder 419)
  - Reporters Without Borders, 2003 (Box 49, Folder 420)
  - New California Media (NCM) (3 folders), 2003 (Box 49, Folder 421-423)
  - Independent Press Association (IPA) - Background (7 folders), 2004 (Box 49, Folder 424-427, Box 50, Folder 428-430)
    Publications, Magazines, Reports
  - Vector III (2 folders), 2004-2005 (Box 50, Folder 431-432)
    Task Force on Grant Making, Monitoring and Accountability; Attachments
  - Teamwork (2 folders), 2000-2002 (Box 50, Folder 433-434)
    Reports and drafts
  - Margaret Wilkerson - Field Analysis, 2000-2001 (Box 50, Folder 435)
  - Program Leadership, 2005 March (Box 50, Folder 436)
    Includes: Diversity in the Grant-making of the Ford Foundation; Preparing Preliminary FY 2006-2007 Program Budgets; Draft Summary of The Ford Foundation's IT Strategic Plan; Learning and Evaluation Vector III Recommendation; Future of the Grant File - Transitioning to a Digital Grant File; California Poll of Asian-Americans on the Tsunami; A Sythesis of Plans and Ideas for Managing Grant Portfolios as Submitted by Program Directors and Overseas Representatives
  - Roberta Uno Portfolio, 2001-2005 (Box 51, Folder 437)
  - Betsy Richards, 2004-2005 (Box 51, Folder 438)
    Memos and Correspondence
  - Replenishing Democracy Report, Elora Chowdhury, KCF Retreat, 2003 October (Box 51, Folder 439)
  - World Culture Forum (PWONO) (2 folders), 2001-2002 (Box 51, Folder 440-441)
    Institute for Cultural Enterprise and World Culture Forum: Structural Assessment and Summary Report; World Culture Forum: Organizational Development Plan; The World Culture Forum: Concept Outline; Participant Bios
  - John Phillip Santos Portfolio, 2001-2003 (Box 51, Folder 442)
    Correspondence; Memos; Digital Independence; Africa Soap Summit: Making Entertainment Useful; Media Projects Fund Reorganization Document
  - Asian Americans/Pacific Islanders in Philanthropy, 2002-2005 (Box 51, Folder 443)
  - Asian American Journalists Association (AAJA) Visions 2020, 2005 (Box 51, Folder 444)
  - Workplans (4 folders), 1999-2006 (Box 51, Folder 445-448)
  - Trustees, 2004 September (Box 52, Folder 449)
  - Trustees, 2004 May (Box 52, Folder 450)
  - Trustees - Cairo Visit, 2002-2006 (Box 52, Folder 451)
  - Trustees, 2005 January (Box 52, Folder 452)
  - Trustees, 2005 May (Box 52, Folder 453)
  - Trustees, 2005 September (Box 52, Folder 454)
  - Trustees, 2006 January (Box 52, Folder 455)
  - Lagos - Media, Arts, and Culture - Program Officer, 2005-2007 (Box 52, Folder 456)
  - Jon Funabiki's Chron Files, 1995-1999 (Box 54, Folder 458-60, Box 55, Folder 461-464, Box 56, Folder 465-468)
  - Trustees - Will the Circle Be Unbroken?, 1998 September (Box 57, Folder 469)
  - Unity - Application and Flyer List, 1998 July (Box 57, Folder 470)
  - Support Initiative to News Media and Diversity Initiative, 1998 (Box 57, Folder 471)
  - World Bank Group Meeting, 1997-1998 (Box 57, Folder 472)
  - Native American Media Initiative, 1998 (Box 57, Folder 473)
  - Quarterly Meetings, 1998 (Box 57, Folder 474)
  - Budget Projections, 1998 (Box 57, Folder 475)
  - New Proposal Guidelines - Grant Application Checklist, 1998 (Box 57, Folder 476)
  - Team Initiative - Meeting Followup, 1998 (Box 57, Folder 477)
  - Pre-Grant Assessment, 1996 (Box 57, Folder 478)